Guide to the Azalea Society of America Records
Azalea Society of America Records
- Publications, 1933-2013; 1933 2013; 25.77 linear feet
  - The Azalean, 1979-2009
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 3 (2 of 4), 1993 September (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 3 (3 of 4), 1993 September (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 3 (4 of 4), 1993 September (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 4, 1993 December (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 4. Articles, 1993 December (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 4. Correspondence, 1993 December (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 15 No. 4. Publication Information, 1993 December (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 1, 1994 March (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 1. Advertisements, 1994 March (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 1. Articles, 1994 March (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 1. Correspondence, 1994 March (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 2, 1994 June (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 2. Articles, 1994 June (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 2. Miscellaneous, 1994 June (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 3 (1 of 4), 1994 September (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 3 (2 of 4), 1994 September (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 3 (3 of 4), 1994 September (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 3 (4 of 4), 1994 September (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 4 (1 of 3), 1994 December (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 4 (2 of 3), 1994 December (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 4 (3 of 3), 1994 December (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 16 No. 4. Advertisements, 1994 December (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 1, 1995 March (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 1. Advertising, 1995 March (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 1. Articles, 1995 March (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 1. Correspondence, 1995 March (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 1. Miscellaneous, 1995 March (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 1. Photographs, 1995 March (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 2, 1995 June (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 2. Advertising, 1995 June (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 2. Articles, 1995 June (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 2. Correspondence, 1995 June (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 2. Miscellaneous, 1995 June (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 2. Photographs, 1995 June (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 3, 1995 September (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 3. Advertising, 1995 September (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 3. Articles, 1995 September (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 3. Correspondence, 1995 September (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 3. Photographs, 1995 September (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 4 (1 of 4), 1995 December (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 4 (2 of 4), 1995 December (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 4 (3 of 4), 1995 December (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 17 No. 4 (4 of 4), 1995 December (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 1 (1 of 9), 1996 March (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 1 (2 of 9), 1996 March (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 1 (3 of 9), 1996 March (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 1 (4 of 9), 1996 March (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 1 (5 of 9), 1996 March (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 1 (6 of 9), 1996 March (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 1 (7 of 9), 1996 March (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 1 (8 of 9), 1996 March (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 1 (9 of 9), 1996 March (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 2 (1 of 6), 1996 June (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 2 (2 of 6), 1996 June (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 2 (3 of 6), 1996 June (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 2 (4 of 6), 1996 June (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 2 (5 of 6), 1996 June (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 2 (6 of 6), 1996 June (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 3 (1 of 4), 1996 September (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 3 (2 of 4), 1996 September (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 3 (3 of 4), 1996 September (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 3 (4 of 4), 1996 September (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 3. Correspondence, 1996 September (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 4 (1 of 4), 1996 December (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 4 (2 of 4), 1996 December (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 4 (3 of 4), 1996 December (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 4 (4 of 4), 1996 December (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 4. Articles, 1996 December (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 18 No. 4. Correspondence, 1996 December (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 1 (1 of 3), 1997 March (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 1 (2 of 3), 1997 March (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 1 (3 of 3), 1997 March (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 2 (1 of 3), 1997 June (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 2 (2of 3), 1997 June (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 2 (3 of 3), 1997 June (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 3 (1 of 4), 1997 September (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 3 (2 of 4), 1997 September (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 3 (3 of 4), 1997 September (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No. 3 (4 of 4), 1997 September (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No.4 (1 of 4), 1997 December (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No.4 (2 of 4), 1997 December (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No.4 (3 of 4), 1997 December (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 19 No.4 (4 of 4), 1997 December (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 1 (1 of 4), 1998 March (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 1 (2 of 4), 1998 March (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 1 (3 of 4), 1998 March (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 1 (4 of 4), 1998 March (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 2 (1 of 4), 1998 June (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 2 (2 of 4), 1998 June (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 2 (3 of 4), 1998 June (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 2 (4 of 4), 1998 June (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 3 (1 of 4), 1998 September (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 3 (2 of 4), 1998 September (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 3 (3 of 4), 1998 September (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 3 (4 of 4), 1998 September (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 4 (1 of 7), 1998 December (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 4 (2 of 7), 1998 December (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 4 (3 of 7), 1998 December (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 4 (4 of 7), 1998 December (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 4 (5 of 7), 1998 December (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 4 (6 of 7), 1998 December (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 20 No. 4 (7 of 7), 1998 December (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 21 No. 1 (1 of 4), 1999 March (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 21 No. 1 (2 of 4), 1999 March (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 21 No. 1 (3 of 4), 1999 March (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 21 No. 1 (4 of 4), 1999 March (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 21 No. 2 (1 of 2), 1999 June (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 21 No. 2 (2 of 2), 1999 June (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files. Volume 21 No. 4, 1999 December (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Spring 1 of 3, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Spring 2 of 3, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Spring 3 of 3, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Summer 1 of 4, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Summer 2 of 4, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Summer 3 of 4, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Summer 4 of 4, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Fall 1 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Fall 2 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Fall 3 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Fall 4 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Fall 5 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Winter 1 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Winter 2 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Winter 3 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Winter 4 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2001 Winter 5 of 5, 2000-2001 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Spring 1 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Spring 2 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Spring 3 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Spring 4 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Summer 1 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Summer 2 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Summer 4 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Fall 1 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Fall 2 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Fall 3 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Fall 4 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Winter 1 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Winter 2 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2002 Winter 3 of 4, 2001-2002 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Spring 1 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Spring 2 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Spring 3 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Spring 4 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Summer 1 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Summer 2 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Summer 3 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Summer 4 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Fall 1 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Fall 2 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Fall 3 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Fall 4 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Winter 1 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Winter 2 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Winter 3 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2003 Winter 4 of 4, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Spring 1 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Spring 2 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Spring 3 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Spring 4 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Summer 1 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Summer 2 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Summer 3 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Summer 4 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Fall 1 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Fall 2 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Fall 3 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Fall 4 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Winter 1 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Winter 2 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Winter 3 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files 2004 Winter 4 of 4, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Spring 1 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Spring 2 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Spring 3 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Spring 4 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Summer 1 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Summer 2 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Summer 3 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Summer 4 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Summer, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Fall 1 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Fall 2 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Fall 3 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Fall 4 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Winter 1 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Winter 2 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Winter 3 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Issue Production Files 2005 Winter 4 of 4, 2004-2005 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Postal Records and Procedures (1 of 2), 1986-1999 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Postal Records and Procedures (2 of 2), 1986-1999 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Presidents Column drafts, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Printing materials collected durring ASA conventions, 1997-2001 (Flatfile 5)
    - The Azalean. Advertising, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - The Azalean. Back Issues, 1984-2004 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - The Azalean. Best Article Ballots, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - The Azalean. Best Article Ballots, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1988-1999 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1991 January-May (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1991 June-December (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1993 January-May (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1993 June-December (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1994 January-May (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1994 June-December (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - The Azalean. Correspondence, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - The Azalean. Miscellaneous, 1984-1996 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - The Azalean. Publication Schedule, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - The Azalean. Volume 1 Number 1-2, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - The Azalean. Volume 2 Number 1-4, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - The Azalean. Volume 3 Number 1-4, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - The Azalean. Volume 4 Number 1-4, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - The Azalean. Volume 5 Number 1-4, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - The Azalean. Volume 6 Number 1-4, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - The Azalean. Volume 7 Number 1-4, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - The Azalean. Volume 8 Number 1-4, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - The Azalean. Volume 9 Number 1-4, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - The Azalean. Volume 10 Number 1-4, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - The Azalean. Volume 11 Number 1-4, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - The Azalean. Volume 12 Number 1-4, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - The Azalean. Volume 13 Number 1-4, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - The Azalean. Volume 14 Number 1-4, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - The Azalean. Volume 15 Number 1-4, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - The Azalean. Volume 16 Number 1-4, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - The Azalean. Volume 17 Number 1-4, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - The Azalean. Volume 18 Number 1-4, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - The Azalean. Volume 19 Number 1-4, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - The Azalean. Volume 20 Number 1-4, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - The Azalean. Volume 21 Number 1-4, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - The Azalean. Volume 22 Number 1-4, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - The Azalean. Volume 22, Numbers 1, 3-4, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - The Azalean. Volume 23 Number 1-4, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - The Azalean. Volume 23, Number 3, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - The Azalean. Volume 24 Number 1-4, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - The Azalean. Volume 24, Numbers 3-4, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - The Azalean. Volume 25 Number 1-4, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - The Azalean. Volume 26 Number 1-4, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - The Azalean. Volume 26, Number 4, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - The Azalean. Volume 27 Number 1-4, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - The Azalean. Volume 27, Numbers 3-4, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - The Azalean. Volume 28, Numbers 1-4, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - The Azalean. Volume 29, Numbers 1-4, 2007 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - The Azalean, Volume 30, Numbers 1, 3, 4, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - The Azalean, Volume 31, Numbers 1, 3, 4, 2009 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - The Azalean, Volume 32, Numbers 2-3, 2010-2011; 2010 2011 (Halfbox 67, Folder 1)
    - The Azalean, Volume 33, Numbers 1-2, 2011 (Halfbox 67, Folder 2)
    - The Azalean, Volume 33, Number 3 & 4, Fall 2011 (Halfbox 67, Folder 3)
    - The Azalean, Volume 34, Number 2 Summer 2012 (Halfbox 67, Folder 4)
    - The Azalean, Volume 34, Number 4, Winter 2013 (Halfbox 67)
    - The Azalean, Volume 35, Number 1, Spring 2013 (Halfbox 67, Folder 4)
    - The Azalean, Volume 35, Number 2, Summer 2013 (Halfbox 67, Folder 4)
    - The Azalean. Volume 35, Number 3, Fall 2013, 0.0050 linear feet (Halfbox 67)
  - Other Publications of the Azalea Society of America, 1933-2007
    - Ben Morrison Chapter newsletter, 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Brochures, undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Brochures. Drafts, undated (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Newsletters. Ben Morrison Chapter, 1986-1989 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Newsletters. Ben Morrison Chapter, 2001-2005 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Newsletters: Ben Morrison Chapter, 2006-2007 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Newsletters. Brookside Gardens Chapter, 1980-1989, 1991, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Newsletters: Brookside Gardens Chapter, 1983-2006 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Newsletters: Brookside Gardens Chapter, 2006-2007 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters. Delmarva Chapter, 1990, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Newsletters. Flame Chapter, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Newsletters. Northern Virginia Chapter, 1981-2005 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters: Northern Virginia Chapter, 2006 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters. Northwest Chapter, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Newsletters. Oconee Chapter, 1992-1998 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Newsletters. Oconee Chapter, 2001-2005 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters: Oconee Chapter, 2006-2007 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Newsletters. Richmond Chapter, 1986-1989 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters. Vaseyi Chapter, 2002-2005 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Newsletters: Vaseyi Chapter, 2005-2007 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Oconee Chapter newsletter, 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Oconee Chapter Newsletter Article Index, 2007 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Vaseyi Chapter newsletter, 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Yearbook, 1933 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Publications of Other Organizations, 1982-2009
    - 1997 Georgia on My Mind official travel guide (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - American Rhododendron Society, 1982, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - American Rhododendron Society Chapter Newsletters, 1999-2001 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - American Rhododendron Society Newsletters, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Azalea small books and pamphlets photocopy, 1977-2006 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Cooperative Extension Service, University of Maryland, 1981-1989, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Editorial Eye, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Gardening in the Lower Midwest by Diane Heileman, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Gardens and Nurseries, 1986-1994, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Growing Azaleas and Rhododendrons, USDA Home and Garden Bulletin, No. 71, 1980 (Halfbox 39, Folder 1)
    - Holly Society of America, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Horticulture Magazines, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Hortideas, 1989 September (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - International Bonsai, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - International Symposium of Kurume-Azalea (in Japanese with English translation, including a paper by John Creech), 1989? (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Kron, Kathleen A., Papers, 1993-1999 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Magazine articles, 1955, 1984, 1992, undated (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - National convention related brochures and printed materials, 1997-2001 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1978-2005 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Non ASA Publications and Newsletters, 1982-2002 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - North Carolina State University. Dept. of Plant Pathology, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Plant Catalogs, Azalea Acres Farm, 1976-1981 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Plant Catalog, RareFind Nursery, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Plant Catalog, RareFind Nursery, 2009 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Plant Catalogs, 1971-1988 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Southern Living, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 21)